<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ducnv6 blog on Viet Duc</title><link>https://tomgermanyyyy.github.io/my-homepage/</link><description>Recent content in ducnv6 blog on Viet Duc</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 17:38:50 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tomgermanyyyy.github.io/my-homepage/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>System Design</title><link>https://tomgermanyyyy.github.io/my-homepage/posts/system-design/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 17:38:50 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://tomgermanyyyy.github.io/my-homepage/posts/system-design/</guid><description>Hello everyone, this is my first blog. Today we will have a discussion on System Design.
Introduction In this era, writing blog is very popular, especially for software developers. They can write blog to get deeper understanding about a concept, a problem, or a technology as well as improve their writing skill and share knowledge to people.
Write a blog for just yourself or a few people to read is easy, but when the number of users scale up, the transactions per second (tps) may increase rapidly, how can your system handle this situation?</description></item><item><title>Some information about milk tea</title><link>https://tomgermanyyyy.github.io/my-homepage/posts/milk-tea/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 17:38:50 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://tomgermanyyyy.github.io/my-homepage/posts/milk-tea/</guid><description>Introduction The term &amp;ldquo;milk tea&amp;rdquo; refers to any tea drink with milk added. It can be as simple as a splash of milk in a hot cup of tea, or it can be a complex recipe including various ingredients, like the popular bubble tea. Adding milk mellows and smooths out the flavors of tea, particularly some of the bitter notes found in black tea. Milk tea is enjoyed throughout the world as both a hot and cold beverage.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://tomgermanyyyy.github.io/my-homepage/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tomgermanyyyy.github.io/my-homepage/about/</guid><description>Hi, my name is Duc. I am a Software Development Fresher at ZaloPay.
I am also a third-year student at Ho Chi Minh City University of Technology - Vietnam National University, majoring in Computer Science. I&amp;rsquo;m an ambitious problem solver with a passion for software development. I&amp;rsquo;m eager to learn new things which will help the team in which I will work to meet its milestones. I have some experiences in ReactJS, Express.</description></item><item><title>Tags</title><link>https://tomgermanyyyy.github.io/my-homepage/tags/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tomgermanyyyy.github.io/my-homepage/tags/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>